so what is emptiness some people say
close your eyes everything is black
black black
black uh that's not emptiness some
people say close your eyes don't think
about
anything my teacher said if you want to
do that meditation you can drink some
beer it's
okay then you don't think about
anything uh then some people say there's
no good thing there's no bad thing just
be happy don't don't think on happy
don't think I'm sad just like
that then this is not emptiness these
are wrong these are own of course nobody
wants to live with somebody who's like
this
only are you happy no are you sad no can
I kiss you I don't
care can I hit you it's all the same you
know then of course this is not
Enlightenment this is not
happiness that's a vegetable or
something so
uh you can learn uh if you learn
emptiness and you want to
make $100 million business you can do
with no experience no I don't have any
business experience right and I don't
like it but I know the secret how I know
Cara I know how to use it and if you
want to have a beautiful relationship
you can use it people ask me for three
things four things some people will say
I want uh enough money to do anything I
want if I want to go to Brazil I can go
tomorrow you know and I have enough
money to come home and relax you know I
don't have to worry about money some
people ask me for that some people say
uh I don't need the money so much I need
a boyfriend or I need a girlfriend uh I
want to have a child you know people ask
me then some people say no no I have a
back problem I have headaches I have
depression how can I use Karma can I use
Karma to fix my body I want to be young
again like that then some people say I
want peace
inside I just want peace and then some
people say I want peace in the world I
don't want to see poor people I don't
want to see War these are things that
people ask me then if you want those
things you have to plant Karma you have
to know how to plant Karma so so I'm
going to talk about it tonight
then you can have all of them actually
okay you don't have to choose you know
why not if you have lots of money you
can help the refugees you can help poor
people you can save Tibetan culture
books we we paid millions of dollars for
25 years then it's good then the money
helps people you can help people with
money then if you have a partner you'll
be much happier two partners can do more
good things than one right like John and
Le young they are more
powerful uh with the partner if you want
to help people it's nice to have a a
good part and it's more fun to have a
partner you come home you can talk about
things you know to sit alone in the
house is not fun and of course you
should have health you should have good
energy why not okay we should have all
of these things and inner peace we
should have
peace and we should try to make peace in
the world so how you have to understand
Karma okay here we
go you have to ask I'm going to ask
question you have to give me answer okay
what is this
thing it's a pen okay second question if
a dog comes in here a small puppy dog
and I go you know and I go like this
what will they do with this
thing they are true on it okay does the
dog see this thing as a pen or
not no they see to something oh look
something to do
okay dog sees two
to human sees a pen next
question who's correct dog or human
who's correct both both you can say both
I think you can say both only one guy in
America in
Florida he said no no dog is
[Music]
wrong only one guy in the whole
world uh dog is
wrong dog can you it's okay the dog said
to the person why are you riding it
tastes so
good so uh of course it both are correct
okay now difficult question
okay you have to learn this question why
tonight we are talking about partner
your boyfriend or girlfriend or wife or
husband we want to make a perfect one
perfect if you already have a partner
you can fix them you can upgrade to
business class or
first okay then if you don't have a
partner you can you can make one with
Karma I'm teaching you Karma this is new
thing new system okay does it work yes
why $200 million okay it works it works
okay no it works I don't know anything
about business nothing but I know about
the pen okay so learn learn the pen okay
next question difficult question if I
put this thing
here all the people go out and all the
dogs go
out at that time which one is it pen or
two
Twi all the people are gone all the dogs
are gone this thing is here now what is
it which one nether yeah who said
neither yeah good in in most countries
somebody in the front will
[Music]
call it's neither one and you're correct
you're right it's neither one at that
time no dog no person didn't it's just
some yellow thing right some yellow
thing if the dog comes in it becomes a c
CTI if the person comes in it becomes a
pen if both of them come in P energy it
becomes both okay and if they both
leave then
it's nothing just nothing that's the
meaning of emptiness okay that's the
meaning of emptiness uh what you call
k k
that's the meaning of that how can you
use that to find a good boyfriend or a
girlfriend how can you use that to fix
your wife or your husband okay this
tonight we have to learn that okay you
don't have to struggle you don't have to
fight some lady came to me okay I give
you a real oh now I have to ask you one
more
question
so is when I see
pen is the pen coming from me from my
mind or is the pen coming from the pen
which one you you must be from me must
be from me
why your
per the dog doesn't see pen if the pen
is coming from the pen the dog will see
a pen the dog will write some
poetry to his dog girlfriend
you have a nice
tail okay but they don't do that why the
the pen is not coming from the pen the
pen is coming from me it must be true
because the dog doesn't see a pen it
must be true okay so can I close my eyes
and I say I don't want a pen I want a
big diamond you know it's coming from
me you know I will use positive
thinking I want a diamond I want a
diamond it's coming from
me oh it's still pant okay it's very
interesting is it coming from me yes can
I control
it no okay then why is it coming from me
there's a scene in my mind I have a
scene in my mind okay it's very
interesting then that se when I look at
this thing when when when Michael looks
at this thing that seed opens in one
second I I go like
this what is this and when I go like
this if you are human a seed opens in
your mind and you see a pen the pen is
coming from the seed in your mind to
this thing it's this big the pen in your
mind is this big Karma OPP Karma means a
sin right Karma means a SE the seed
opens in your mind a little picture
comes
out and oh look pen you see it's very
fast you can do 65 times in 1 second
Buddha said 65 times in 1
second divide 1 second by 65 that's how
long it takes for the seed to open and
come to this pen okay and you are doing
it with everything okay this building
askla your friends your hand
me everything's coming from you
everything's coming out of your mind so
if you don't like my talk it's your
fault
okay now everything is coming from from
our mind okay from a seed in my mind
question question how to plant the seed
how to plant the seed then you can make
$200 million it's easy just plant a seat
don't go work so hard I work 6 months I
take 6 month vacation this is correct
system right some people work 50 weeks
they take two week vacation I say you
are crazy you are crazy okay work 6
months relax 6
months good system okay if you
understand sin you can do that okay you
just have to understand the see Diamond
color sudra just understand tonight you
can understand then use it for the rest
of your life John and Leon can teach you
they studied it for many years you are
very lucky to have them I think you
should kidnap them and tie them up if
I'm from Norway I will tie them up you
know you cannot go
home okay cuz they are a really good
teachers they can teach you the details
but tonight I will just teach you
roughly so question how do I if I want
to have a boyfriend or girlfriend let's
say I don't have a partner I try to have
a partner but Paul a
Monday then how do I how do I put the
seed for a good partner how do I plant
the seed then they will come to you you
don't have